Aleksandra Paskovska Vidanovski

Bitola, Pelagonia, North Macedonia



aleksandra.paskovska@hotmail.com



+389 076 222 644



linkedin.com/in/aleksandra-paskovska-vidanovski



https://dribbble.com/paskovska

Summary

Graphic and UX/UI Designer. Great team player, skilled in Figma, Adobe XD, Photoshop, Illustrator, InVision, Branding, and Logo Design. In my previous work experience, I have worked on several projects for mobile and web applications, as well as logos, posters, calendars, notebooks, book covers, and complete branding.

Experience



Graphic and UI/UX Designer

Inellipse

Dec 2018 - Present (4 years 4 months)

Raster and vector graphics, Web design, and Mobile applications design in Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD, and Figma.



Intern

Inellipse

Jun 2018 - Nov 2018 (6 months)

Raster and vector graphics in Adobe Illustrator and Adobe Photoshop.

Quality Assurance Specialist

Taskforce

May 2017 - Aug 2017 (4 months) Installing Amazon lockers in Adobe

Graphic Designer

Self Employment

Aug 2013 - May 2018 (4 years 10 months)

Work in Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, and Adobe InDesign. On Branding and Logo Design projects.

Education



Brainster

UX/UI Design

2021 - 2022

User Flows, Prototyping, Testing, Wireframes, Storytelling, Web, App



Faculty of Technical Sciences, St. Kliment Ohridski University - Bitola

University graduate engineer in a Graphical Engineering at Technical Faculty - Bitola, Graphic Engineering 2009 - 2013

Licenses & Certifications

- Certificate for successfully completing the Graphic design course (3D Maya) CAD-LAIF
- Learning transform lives project YES Network EDC (Education Development Center)
- Project YES Network Introductory module, Personal Development, appropriate behavior in the workplace, communication skills, teamwork, and leadership skills for job search, security, rights and responsibilities in the workplace, financial skills USAID
- Business without borders project For business planning USAID

Skills

Creativity Skills • Visual Storytelling • Problem Solving • Branding • Visual Design • Design Strategy • Wireframing • Prototyping • Research • Information Architecture